<resources>
    <!-- General App strings -->
    <string name="app_name">Fit Notifications</string>
    <string name="app_icon">Fit Notifications App Icon</string>
    <string name="other_app_icon">App icon of an installed app</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="app_info">Fit Notifications Menu</string>
    <string name="instructions">Start interactive setup</string>
    <string name="instructions_manual">Show manual setup instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions_manual_heading">Show manual setup instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions_heading">Setup</string>
    <string name="faqs">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="whats_new">What\'s new</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="app_choices">Select Apps to Enable Notifications</string>
    <string name="app_choices_activity_title">Select Apps</string>
    <string name="enabled_apps_filter_menu">Filter Enabled Apps</string>
    <string name="notification_service_started">Fit Notifications Service started</string>
    <string name="notification_text">[Relayed notification] Go to settings to enable auto-dismiss.</string>
    <string name="test_notification_text">[Placeholder notification] Go to settings to enable auto-dismiss.</string>
    <string name="test_notification">Test Notification</string>
    <string name="test_notification_sent">Test notification sent</string>
    <string name="notification_access">Notification Access</string>
    <string name="enable_notification_access">Enable Notification Access</string>
    <string name="disable_notification_access">Disable Notification Access</string>
    <string name="start_service_info_text">Starting the notification service&#8230;</string>
    <string name="start_service">Start Service</string>
    <string name="stop_service">Stop Service</string>
    <string name="search_menu">App search</string>

    <!-- Intro Strings Activity -->
    <string name="intro_get_started_button">Get started</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_title">Get all your notifications on your Fitbit device</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_desc">This app is designed for use with the Fitbit platform. It requires the official Fitbit app, and is compatible with Fitbit Alta, Blaze and Surge. We are not affiliated with Fitbit, Inc.</string>

    <string name="intro_enable_access_title">First, enable notification access</string>
    <string name="intro_enable_access_desc">You must enable notification access for this app and the official Fitbit app. Click the button below, and then enable access for both apps in the next screen.</string>

    <string name="intro_enable_access_update_title">Notification access enabled</string>
    <string name="intro_enable_access_update_desc">Nice, We now have notification access! Let\'s move on to the next step.</string>

    <string name="intro_enable_access_success_title">Great, you already enabled notification access!</string>
    <string name="intro_enable_access_success_desc">This app requires notification access to work. And looks like you have already enabled it! Move on to the next step!</string>

    <string name="intro_get_fitbit_title">Install the official Fitbit app!</string>
    <string name="intro_get_fitbit_desc">Looks like you don\'t have the official Fitbit app installed. We\'ll need that, so let\'s install it by clicking the button below.</string>
    <string name="intro_get_fitbit_button">Install Fitbit app</string>

    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_title1">Setup notifications in Fitbit app: Step 1</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_title2">Setup notifications in Fitbit app: Step 2</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_title3">Setup notifications in Fitbit app: Step 3</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_desc1">First, go into device settings by clicking the device icon in the Fitbit app.</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_toast_text1">Only Fitbit Alta, Blaze and Surge models are compatible!</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_toast_button">Compatible Fitbit devices</string>

    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_desc2">Select \'Call and Text Notifications\' under \'General\'. Then, Select \'Text Notifications\' under \'Settings\'.</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_desc3">Choose \'Fit Notifications\'. Then, sync your Fitbit device within the Fitbit app. Do not choose this app for Call/Calendar Notifications, otherwise you will NOT get any notifications.</string>
    <string name="intro_setup_fitbit_button3">Open Fitbit app</string>
    <string name="intro_get_fitbit_toast_text3">Fitbit app not found! Go back and install the official Fitbit app!</string>

    <string name="intro_select_apps_title">Choose the apps you want notifications for</string>
    <string name="intro_select_apps_desc">You can now choose the apps whose notifications you want to receive on your Fitbit device. They will appear like Text Notifications on the device and will have the app name for clarity.</string>

    <string name="intro_start_service_title">Start the notification listening service</string>
    <string name="intro_start_service_desc">This service will try to stay in the background. If you stop receiving notifications, restart the service from this app. Don\'t use task killer apps, as they can disable the service.</string>

    <string name="intro_dnd_mode_title">Do not disturb mode on Android 6.0+ (Marshmallow)</string>
    <string name="intro_dnd_mode_desc">If you enable do not disturb mode, then no notifications will be forwarded to your Fitbit device, by default. To change that, you need to follow specific instructions by clicking below.</string>
    <string name="intro_dnd_mode_button">Extra Instructions</string>
    <string name="intro_dnd_mode_message">
    Click on configure below. In the next screen, choose \"Notifications\" and enable \"Treat as priority\".\n\n
    Now, when you use silent mode, enable \"Priority Only\". Doing so will allow you to get notifications via the app on your Fitbit device, but it will not
    make any notification sound on the phone as this app doesn\'t cause notification sounds or vibrations anyway.
    </string>

    <string name="intro_done_title">Done! Test your setup now!</string>
    <string name="intro_done_desc">Click the button below to send a test notification. You will see it on your device if the setup was successful! That\'s the basics! Check out the settings page for additional features!</string>


    <!-- First launch -->
    <string name="done_first_launch_key">FirstLaunch</string>
    <string name="version_key">AppVersion</string>
    <string name="setup_incomplete">Setup is incomplete! Please review the interactive setup once, even if you successfully configured a previous version of the app. </string>
    <string name="setup_incomplete_title">Incomplete Setup</string>

    <!-- Settings Menu -->
    <!-- Settings Menu headings -->
    <string name="settings_menu">Settings</string>
    <string name="save_settings">Save Settings</string>
    <string name="placeholder_notif_settings">Placeholder Notification Settings</string>
    <string name="relayed_notif_settings">Relayed Notification Settings</string>
    <string name="limit_notif_settings">Notification Limit Settings</string>
    <string name="debug_settings">Troubleshooting Settings</string>

    <string name="dismiss_placeholder_notif">Dismiss Placeholder Notification</string>
    <string name="dismiss_placeholder_notif_summary">Enable this to automatically dismiss the placeholder notification from the Fit Notifications app, after a delay</string>
    <string name="dismiss_placeholder_notif_key">DismissAppNotification</string>

    <string name="dismiss_relayed_notif">Dismiss Relayed Notifications</string>
    <string name="dismiss_relayed_notif_summary">Enable this to automatically dismiss the relayed notification, after a delay</string>
    <string name="dismiss_relayed_notif_key">DismissOtherNotifications</string>

    <string name="limit_notif">Limit Number of Relayed Notifications</string>
    <string name="limit_notif_summary">Enable this to limit the number of notifications relayed to your Fitbit device from each app\n\nUse this if you receive too many notifications on your device in a short duration</string>
    <string name="limit_notif_key">limitNotifications</string>

    <string name="notif_limit_duration">Limit Duration</string>
    <string name="notif_limit_duration_key">NotiflimitDuration</string>
    <string name="notif_limit_duration_summary0">All notifications are sent as they arrive, without limitation.</string>
    <plurals name="notif_limit_duration_summary">
        <item quantity="one">Relay one notification every %1$d second for each enabled app\n\nAdditional notifications are discarded</item>
        <item quantity="other">Relay one notification every %1$d seconds for each enabled app\n\nAdditional notifications are discarded</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="placeholder_dismiss_delay">Delay</string>
    <string name="placeholder_dismiss_delay_summary0">Placeholder notification from this app will not be dismissed automatically.</string>
    <plurals name="placeholder_dismiss_delay_summary">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d second, then dismiss placeholder notification\n\nChoose a higher delay if you don\'t get the notification on your Fitbit device</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d seconds, then dismiss placeholder notification\n\nChoose a higher delay if you don\'t get the notification on your Fitbit device</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="placeholder_dismiss_delay_key">PlaceholderDismissDelay</string>

    <string name="relayed_dismiss_delay">Delay</string>
    <string name="relayed_dismiss_delay_summary0">Relayed notification will not be dismissed automatically.</string>
    <plurals name="relayed_dismiss_delay_summary">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d second, then dismiss relayed notification</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d seconds, then dismiss relayed notification</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="relayed_dismiss_delay_key">RelayedDismissDelay</string>

    <string name="override_interactive_setup_key">overrideInteractiveSetupKey</string>
    <string name="override_interactive_setup_enabled_summary">Override it. Interactive setup is disabled and will show original manual setup instructions instead.</string>
    <string name="override_interactive_setup_disabled_summary">Do not override. Interactive setup is enabled.</string>
    <string name="override_interactive_setup_title">Override Interactive Setup</string>

    <!-- App Choice Activity -->
    <string name="app_list_loading_text">Loading app list&#8230;</string>
    <string name="app_list_empty_search">No apps fit your search criteria.</string>
    <string name="search_query_hint">Type app name&#8230;</string>

    <!-- HTML Information -->
    <string name="about_app_text"><![CDATA[
    <p>Fit Notifications is a third party application that allows you to send notifications from any of the apps installed on your phone to your compatible Fitbit device.
       In order to properly setup this application, please follow the provided instructions.</p>
	<p>Please note that neither \'Fit Notifications\' nor \'Smart Dinosaurs Entertainment\' is affiliated with Fitbit, Inc. in anyway.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="instructions_text"><![CDATA[
    <p>To properly set up this application, please follow the instructions below:</p>
    <ol>
        <li>Enable notification access to this application by clicking the \'Notification Access\' button.</li><br/>
        <li>In the Fitbit app, go into your device settings by clicking the device icon*.</li><br/>
        <li>Select \'Text Notifications\' or \'Call and Text Notifications\' under \'General\'.</li><br/>
        <li>Select \'Text Notifications\' under \'Settings\'.</li><br/>
        <li>Choose \'Fit Notifications\'. Sync your Fitbit device within the Fitbit app.</li>
        <p><b>NOTE:</b> Do not choose \'Fit Notifications\' for \'Call Notifications\' or \'Calendar Notifications\' in the Fitbit app! Doing so will cause this app to not work!</p>

        <li>In the \'Fit Notifications\' app, go to \'Select Apps to Enable Notifications\'. Then,
            choose the apps whose notifications you would like to be sent to your compatible Fitbit device.</li><br/>
        <li>Click the \'Start Service\' button when you want to start the notification service provided by this app.
            Click the \'Stop Service\' button to stop the service. You must keep the Fitbit app from Fitbit, Inc.
            installed at all times and pair your Fitbit device to the phone for this to work. Enjoy!</li><br />
        <li><b>NOTE:</b> If you use a device running Android 6.0 or above and you enable \"Do Not Disturb\" mode, also
            called silent mode, then please follow the additional instructions below.</li>
    </ol>
    <p style=\"font-size:70%;\">* You must have a compatible Fitbit device, such as Fitbit Alta, Blaze or Surge.</p>
    <p>Future updates will further refine the feature set of this app! Please provide feedback on Google Play if
       there are any issues and if you like this app, kindly provide or update your review!</p>

    <h3>Enabling notifications when using \"Do Not Disturb\" mode</h3>
    <p>Due to the new \"Do Not Disturb\" mode in Android 6.0, if you use this mode (also called silent mode) then you
    will not receive notifications on your Fitbit device as Android disables notification forwarding. To avoid
    this issue manually, you have to change the notifications priority for Fit Notifications app.</p>

    <p>To do so, go to \"Settings>Apps>Fit Notifications\". Note that this menu may be at a slightly different location on
    your phone. Then, choose \"Notifications\" and enable \"Treat as priority\". Then, when you use silent mode, enable
    \"Priority Only\". Doing so will allow you to get notifications via the app on your Fitbit device, but it will not
    make any notification sound on the phone as this app doesn\'t cause notification sounds or vibrations anyway.</p>

    <h3>Demo</h3>
    <p>Press the demo notification button below to see this app in action! Once you have finished the setup,
    click the demo notification button below. You should then see a notification in the status bar from this app,
    while at the same time you should have received a sample notification on your Fitbit. Then, you have confirmed
    that the application is working correctly! Issues? Please contact us!</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="faqs_text"><![CDATA[
    <p><b>Q. Is my Fitbit device supported?</b></p>
    <p>This app can only work with Fitbit Alta, Blaze and Surge, i.e. those devices where you can set a text notification.
       Unfortunately, Fitbit, Inc. has recently changed the behavior for 3rd party call notifications on Charge and Charge HR.
       Hence those devices are not compatible with this app. Fitbit, Inc. may modify the behavior of text notifications at any
       time for the compatible devices. This is not in our control.</p>
    <p><b>Q. Will this app ever stop working as advertised?</b></p>
    <p>If Fitbit, Inc. decides to change the behavior of text notifications from 3rd party apps such as this, then unfortunately
       \'Fit Notifications\' may stop working. We will try to update the app in case of such issues. Please report such issues to us.</p>
    <p><b>Q. I am not getting any notifications on my Fitbit device. Why?</b></p>
    <p>Please ensure that your Fitbit device is one of the supported devices. Also, ensure that you have the official Fitbit app from
       Fitbit, Inc. Make sure that you followed all the instructions, including enabling notification access to \'Fitbit Notifications\'.
       Also, ensure that you can sync to your Fitbit device by enabling Bluetooth (location services should also be enabled on newer Android devices).</p>
    <p><b>Q. I still cannot get notifications! Why?</b></p>
    <p>Make sure you have enabled the notification feature on your Fitbit device. Additionally, ensure that the \'Fit Notifications\'
       service is running by pressing \'Start Service\' button below. This service MAY be stopped by Android on occasion. Do not use task
       killers as they can stop the service needed by this app to function. Finally, you can press the demo notification button below to
       test the functionality while you troubleshoot the problem.</p>
    <p>Other reasons as to why the app is not working include:</p>
    <ul>
        <li>low battery on your Fitbit device: the Fitbit app may disable Notifications if your Fitbit device has low battery.</li>
        <li>Your Fitbit device may require a reboot to enable notifications, due to errors. Refer to the Fitbit website to find out how to reboot your device.</li>
        <li>You may need to reselect \'Fit Notifications\' as described in Step 5 in the instructions.</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Q. Can this app function if I use task killers on my phone?</b></p>
    <p>Please note that task killers may interfere with the proper functioning of this app. It is recommended that you disable task
       killers or at least allow them to keep the \'Fit Notifications\' service running.</p>
    <p><b>Q. Why am I not getting notifications from a particular app on my phone?</b></p>
    <p>Make sure that you have selected the app for which you want to see notifications on your compatible Fitbit device - refer to
        step 6 of the instructions. If you still have issues, and followed the instructions correctly, then please contact us via
       email to inform us the name of the application (including Google Play Store link) for which you are missing notifications.
       We will attempt to resolve this issue in an update.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="whats_new_text"><![CDATA[
    <p>You just updated to Fit Notifications <b>version 2.3.1</b>! The following changes are made in this version:</p>
    <ul>
        <li>New troubleshooting settings option: \"Override Interactive Setup\" <br /><br />
        Use this feature if you have issues with the new (BETA) interactive setup mode, or simply prefer the original, manual setup! Let us know of any issues with the interactive mode, and give detailed information about your setup to help us debug and fix it.
        <br /><br /></li>
        <li>General user interface improvements and maintenance fixes</li>
    </ul>

    ]]></string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text"><![CDATA[
    <p>Fitbit is a registered trademark and service mark of Fitbit, Inc.
       \'Fit Notifications\' is designed for use with the Fitbit platform. This application
       is not put out by Fitbit, and Fitbit does not service or warrant the functionality of this application.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="credits_text"><![CDATA[
    <p>Developed by Smart Dinosaurs Entertainment</p>
    <p>Lead Software Engineer: <a href=\"https://abhijitvalluri.com\">Abhijit Kiran Valluri</a></p>
    <h4>Contact Information:</h4>
    <p>Support Email: <a href=\"mailto:android@abhijitvalluri.com\">android@abhijitvalluri.com</a></p>
    <p>Support Website: <a href=\"https://android.abhijitvalluri.com\">Smart Dinosaurs Entertainment Website</a></p>
    ]]></string>

</resources>
